(Bernadette:)I don't even
know where to begin.
Well, in The Sound of Music,
Julie Andrews says,
"Let's start at
the very beginning.
A very good place to start."
(Bernadette:)Oh, I was gonna start
at the end.
(Bernadette:)Thank God you're here.
(Raj:)Well, I think the first thing we
should get rid of is that tone.
(Amy:)Sorry.
(Bernadette:)I should probably keep this
(Bernadette:)in case we have a girl.
(Raj:)Oh, that's a nice one.
(Raj:)Was it yours when
you were little?
(Bernadette:)My dad built it for me.
(Raj:)Wow, it's so cute.
(Bernadette:)This was the husband
and this was the wife.
(Bernadette:)They'd go out on
adventures together.
(Bernadette:)Cruises, skiing,
(Bernadette:)horseback riding.
(Bernadette:)That was really me just
duct taping them to our dog.
(Raj:)Oh, and did they have kids?
(Bernadette:)They did, but the mommy
and daddy didn't like them,
(Bernadette:)so they shipped them off
to an orphanage
(Bernadette:)I made out of a shoebox.
(Raj:)Yeah, that's not worrisome
at all.
(Bernadette:)Not every girl dreams
about being a mom.
(Bernadette:)Sometimes you think
you're never gonna have kids